Guide to the Deep Springs College records, 1913-1999.
Deep Springs College records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Deep Springs College records, 1913-1999.
6428
Deep Springs College.
20.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, minutes, published material, manuscripts, and photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Trustees records include minutes, 1923-1996; reports, 1960-1975; and correspondence, 1913-1984. Deep Springs student body records contain minutes, 1917-1999, co-education studies reports, 1979-1994. Also student, community, committee and class projects, 1933-1990's; Telluride Association newsletters, 1915-1983; Telluride Association convention minutes, 1911-1999; and Deep Springs Alumni newsletters, 1966-1999.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Deep Springs College, founded in 1917 by power and mining magnate L. L. Nunn, is located thirty miles from the nearest town, in a high desert valley of eastern California. Mr. Nunn wished his students to learn the value of service and practical knowledge as well as be able to work uninterrupted by the distractions of modern society and learn that freedom requires living in accordance with the ideals and duties of one's community. Each of the 26 male students experiences a broad seminar-style education based on the "three pillars of Deep Springs": academic pursuits, the labor program, and self-governance. Following their time at Deep Springs most students transfer to other institutions of higher learning to earn college degrees.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Trustees records include minutes, 1923-1996; reports, 1960-1975; and correspondence, 1913-1984. Deep Springs student body records contain minutes, 1917-1999, co-education studies reports, 1979-1994. Also student, community, committee and class projects, 1933-1990's; Telluride Association newsletters, 1915-1983; Telluride Association convention minutes, 1911-1999; and Deep Springs Alumni newsletters, 1966-1999. These materials include minutes, reports, correspondence, projects, photograph albums, and newsletters. Includes a manuscript copy of "A History of Deep Springs" with chapters by various authors.
Also, works compiled by Denis E. Clark, 2001, including "Telluride Power: A Brief History of the Early Days," "Nunn Archive Image Index," and three CD-Rs: DEC Nunn Archive Images, vol. 1 and vol. 2 (images of the early days of the Telluride Power Company obtained from various sources), and Deep Springs Archive Photos (images scanned by students at Deep Springs College, mostly Telluride Power Company, but some early Deep Springs)
SUBJECTS
Names:
Deep Springs College.; Nunn, L. L. (Lucien Lucius), 1853-1925.; Nunn, L. L. (Lucien Lucius), 1853-1925; Deep Springs College -- Students.; Deep Springs College -- Trustees.; Deep Springs College -- Alumni and alumnae.; Deep Springs College
Subjects:
College students -- United States.; Education -- United States.; College students; Education; Students; Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae
Places:
United States
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to Box 1 - Box 12, Folder 3 and ledger (Trustee records) is restricted to the permission of the Curator.
Access to Boxes 12-14, Student Body records more than 50 years old is restricted to the permission of the Curator.
Access to Boxes 14-17, Student Body records less than 50 years old is restricted to the permission of the Student Body..
RELATED MATERIALS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Trustees of Deep Springs (TDS)
Series II. Deep Springs Student Body (DSSB) and alumni materials
Series III. Photographs and images
CONTAINER LIST
- Trustees of Deep Springs (TDS), 1913-1992
  Access restricted to the permission of the Curator.
  - Trustees of Deep Springs (TDS) Minutes, 1923-1992
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Minutes May 1923 -- May 1930, 1923-05-1930-05 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - TDS Minutes October 1930 -- December 1935, 1930-10-1935-12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - TDS Minutes May 1936 -- October 1937, 1936-05-1937-10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - TDS Minutes October 1937 -- April 1940, 1937-10-1940-04 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - TDS Minutes May 1940 -- April 1941, 1940-05-1941-04 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - TDS Minutes November 1940 (handwritten manuscript; typewritten version in folder 5), 1940-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - TDS Minutes May 1941 -- November 1941, 1941-05-1941-11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - TDS Minutes May 1942 -- November 1942, 1942-05-1942-11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - TDS Minutes January 1943 -- July 1945, 1943-01-1945-07 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - TDS Minutes July 1945 -- December 1947, 1945-07-1947-12 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - TDS Minutes January 1948 -- January 1951, 1948-01-1951-01 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - TDS Minutes January 1951 -- January 1952, 1951-01-1952-01 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - TDS Minutes February 1952 -- December 1953, 1952-02-1953-12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - TDS Minutes May 1953, 1953-05 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Report of the DSSB Survey Committee to TDS May 1951, 1951-05 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - TDS Minutes May 1954 -- May 1957, 1954-05-1957-05 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - TDS Minutes May 1957 -- October 1958, 1957-05-1958-10 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - TDS Minutes May 1959 -- November 1960, 1959-05-1960-11 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - TDS Minutes May 1961 -- November 1961, 1961-05-1961-11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - TDS Minutes May 1962 -- November 1962, 1962-05-1962-11 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - TDS Minutes May 1963 -- June 1963, 1963-05-1963-06 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - TDS Minutes January 1964 -- November 1964, 1964-01-1964-11 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - TDS Minutes February 1965 -- October 1966, 1965-02-1966-10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - TDS Minutes April 1967 -- November 1973, 1967-04-1973-11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - TDS Minutes 1934-1968, 1934-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - TDS Corporation Minutes 1966-1979, 1966-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - TDS Minutes 1969-1979, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
    - Reports to TDS 1960-1966, 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
    - Reports to TDS 1966-1972, 1966-1972 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Reports to TDS 1972-1975, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
    - TDS Minutes 1973-1980, 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
    - TDS Minutes 1980-1986, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
    - TDS Minutes 1980-1986, 3 of 3, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - TDS Minutes 1986-1989, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2-4)
    - TDS Minutes 1989-1990, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    - TDS Minutes 1991-1992, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7-9)
  - Trustees of Deep Springs (TDS) Correspondence, 1913-1984
    - Peale Correspondence, 1913-1928; L.L. Nunn Personal File No. 1363, 1913-1928 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Inyo County Bank, Big Pine, CA; L.L. Nunn Personal File No. 134, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Deep Springs Trust Receipts and Paid Bills 1921-1926, 1921-1926 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - O.B. Suhr; John Stahl; Chas Dickinson 1925-1926, 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Various Correspondence, 1925-1930, 1925-1930 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
    - Decree Approving Final Account and of Final Distribution by Exectuors of Estate of L.L. Nunn, Deceased, dated June 1, 1926, 1926-06-01 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report of Examination as at November 30, 1926, 1926-11-30 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Receipts for Year 1926-1927, 1926-1927 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
    - Inyo County Bank 1927, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Deep Springs, CA; Report of Audit for the Year ended August 31, 1927, 1927-08-31 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Receipts for 1927-1928, 1928-1927 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Statements from General Books of TDS 1927-1928, 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - DSSB Excerpts from the Minutes for TDS, 1927-1938, 1927-1938 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Deep Springs, CA; Report of Audit for the Year ended August 31, 1928, 1928-08-31 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Receipts 1928-1929, 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Deep Springs Statements 1928-1929, 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Repairs to Lucille Ave. House, 1929, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Deep Springs, CA; Report of Audit for the Year ended August 31, 1929, 1929-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Receipts 1929-1930, 1929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs statements; 1929-1930, 1929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Deep Springs, CA; Report of Audit for the Year ended August 31, 1930, 1930-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Receipts 1930-1931, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Statements 1930-1931, 1931-1932, 1930-1932 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs, General Correspondence 1930-1934, 1930-1934 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Deep Springs, CA; Report of Audit for the Year ended August 31, 1931, 1931-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Receipts 1931-1932, 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Statements 1931-1932; Deep Springs, 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - United Milk Products Stockholder's Report 1931-1933, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence TDS 1931-1934, 1931-1934 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Deep Springs, CA; Report of Audit for the Year ended August 31, 1932, 1932-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Statements 1932-1933 Deep Springs and General Trustees of Deep Springs, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Deep Springs Receipts 1932-1933, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1933, 1933-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Receipts TDS 1933-1934, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Statements of Deep Springs 1933-1935, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 23-24)
    - Cattle Audits 1933-1950, 1933-1950 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1934, 1934-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - In re: Sale of L.L.'s Provo Res. Property, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Receipts 1934-1935, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence with William Crawford and Harry Scott 1934-1935, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1935, 1935-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Receipts 1935-1936, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Extra Statements 1935-1936, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with William Crawford, Mike Fellows; Wl. Spalding, L.A. Kimpton 1935-1936; Charles Waldo; Robert Sproull; Morrison Rutherford 1936-1937; 1 of 2, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with William Crawford, Mike Fellows; Wl. Spalding, L.A. Kimpton 1935-1936; Charles Waldo; Robert Sproull; Morrison Rutherford 1936-1937; 2 of 2, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1936, 1936-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Receipts 1936-1937, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Extra Statements 1936-1937, 1938-1939, 1939-1940; 1 of 5, 1936-1940 (Box 5, Folder 9-13)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1937, 1937-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Armand Kelly, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Receipts 1937-1938, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence with Roubert Sproull; Morrison Rutherford; Nathan Bedell 1937-1939, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence; Trustees of Deep Springs 1937-1938, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Correpsondence with L.A. Kimpton 1937-1941, 1937-1941 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Conversion of Oil Heating Plan 1937-1947 [EMPTY], 1937-1947 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Monarch Metal Weatherstrips (1937) [EMPTY], 1937 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Heating and Ventilating System through 1946 [EMPTY], 1946 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - New Cottage 1940 [EMPTY], 1940 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1938, 1938-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Receipts 1938, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - In re: New Trustee (1940), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - TDS Correspondence Roderick MacKenzie 1939; Spalding with Gustafson; Spalding; Tetrault; Sullivan; Mason; Kirkham 1938-1941, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1939, 1939-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs 1939-1940, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Extra 1939-1940 Statements TDS, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs MacKenzie Cattle Settlement 1939-1941, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - In re: MacKenzie Cattle Settlement, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Monthly Statements 1939-1941 June-May, 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs General Correspondence 1939-1944, 1939-1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Reports to Trustees 1939-1946 [EMPTY], 1939-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Trustees Balance Sheets 1939-1948, 1939-1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Household Equipment 1939-1951 [EMPTY], 1939-1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Richfield, UT; Report on Examination of Accounts; for the Year ended August 31, 1940, 1940-08-31 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs 1940 Balance Sheets; 1940 Minutes [EMPTY], 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs 1941 In re: New Trustee, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Trustees of Deep Sprins Receipts 1940-1941, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - TDS Completed April 30, 1941 Statements; Final May 31, 1941 Statements; Reconiliation by Auditors of Deep Springs Cost on Treas: May 31, 1941; Cash sStatements for Year ended May 31, 1941, 1941-08-30 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - SB Trustee 1940-1942, 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - TDS In re: 1941-1942 Budget, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - TDS Statements May 1940-May 1942, 1940-05-1942-05 (Box 6, Folder 14-17)
    - Cattle November 1940 -- November 1949 [EMPTY], 1940-11-1949-11 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Taxes; General 1940-1950, 1940-1950 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - TDS Various Correspondence Etc. 1941, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Teacher's Insurance and Annuity Association 1941, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - TDS Roodouse Report on Water Development May 1941 [EMPTY], 1941-05 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1941, 1941-05-31 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - TDS Correspondence 1941-1942, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
    - Receipts 1941-1942 TDS, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - TDS Correspondence 1941-1944, 1941-1944 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Water Supply and Distribution Through 1945 [EMPTY], 1945 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Monthly Statements 1941-1947, 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 29-31)
    - General 1941-1947, 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - TDS Misc. Correspondence 1941-1949, 1941-1949 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Monthly Statements June 1941 -- May 1944, 1941-06-1944-05 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
    - Personnel 1941 -- April 1950, 1941-1950-04 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Committee of the Whole 1942-1951, 1942-1951 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Food Supplies 1942-1951 [EMPTY], 1942-1951 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Building Insulation Project [EMPTY] (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Extra Statements 1942-1944 [EMPTY], 1942-1944 (Box 6, Folder 40-41)
    - TDS Receipts 1942-1943, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Statements DS 1942-1943; 1 of 2, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Statements DS 1942-1943, 2 of 2, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - TDS Various Correspondence 1942-1943, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1942, 1942-05-31 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1943, 1943-05-31 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - TDS 1943-1944 Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - TDS Receipts 1943-1944, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Trustees 1943-1952, 1943-1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Study Programs 1943-1951, 1943-1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Yards and Gardens 1943 -- February 1951 [EMPTY], 1943-1951-02 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1944, 1944-05-31 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Extra Statements 1944-1945 [EMPTY], 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Maintenance 1945 -- February 1951 [EMPTY], 1945-1951-02 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - TDS School Reports June 1945 -- May 1947, 1945-06-1947-05 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1945, 1945-05-31 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Monthly Statements June 1944 -- May 1947; 1 of 2, 1944-06-1947-05 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Monthly Statements June 1944 -- May 1947; 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1946, 1946-05-31 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Water Supply and Distribution 1946 [EMPTY], 1946 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - TDS Monthly Reports June 1946 -- May 1948, 1946-06-1948-05 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
    - Personnel through 1950, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Northwest Association (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Water Supply and Distribution January 1947 -- May 1947 [EMPTY], 1947-01-1947-05 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Water Supply and Distribution June 1947 -- December 1947 [EMPTY], 1947-06-1947-12 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - TDS Eva Rose Legacy 1947 [EMPTY], 1947 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Public Relations September 1947 -- December 31, 1950, 1947-09-1950-12-31 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - TDS Correspondence June 1945 -- May 1947, 1945-06-1947-05 (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
    - TDS Correspondence 1947-1949, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 30-33)
    - Reports to Trustees 1947-1949 [EMPTY], 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1947, 1947-05-31 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Monthly Statements June 1947 -- May 1948; June 1948 -- May 1949; June 1959 -- May 1950; June 1950 -- May 1951, 1947-06-1951-05 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Heating and Ventilating System 1947-1950 [EMPTY], 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence Out January-June 1948; 1 of 2, 1948-01-1948-06 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence Out January-June 1948; 2 of 2, 1948-01-1948-06 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Applications, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Water System 1948 [EMPTY], 1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 1948 TDS Correspondence, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1948, 1948-05-31 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 1948 TA Convention at Deep Springs, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Teacher's Insurance [EMPTY] (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - TA Alumni TA-DS 1947 -- December 31, 1952, 1947-1952-12-31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - TDS School Reports, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
    - Former Instructors 1947-1951, 1947-1951 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - General 1951, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Correpsondence Out July -- December 1948, 1948-07-1948-12 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
    - DS Policies Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - TDS Monthly Reports June 1948 -- May 1951, 1948-06-1951-05 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Furniture -- Fixtures 1948-1951 [EMPTY], 1948-1951 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Elementary School, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1949, 1949-05-31 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - 1949 TDS Correspondence, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence Out January-June 1949, 1949-01-1949-06 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - July-December 1949; 1 of 2, 1949-07-1949-12 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - July-December 1949; 2 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1950, 1950-05-31 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Water System 1949-1950 [EMPTY], 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Accounting and Finance 1949-1950 [EMPTY], 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Monthly Invoices 1949-1953 [EMPTY], 1949-1953 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Main Building Refurnishment Project [EMPTY] (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Budget 1949-1951, 1949-1951 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - January 1950 -- June 1950, 1950-01-1950-06 (Box 8, Folder 30-31)
    - July 1950 -- December 1950, 1950-07-1950-12 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
    - TDS Monthly Reports June 1, 1950 -- May 31, 1952, 1950-06-01-1952-05-31 (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
    - Deep Springs Survey Committee, Undated (Box 8, Folder 36-37)
    - June 1950 -- May 1952, 1950-06-1952-05 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - June 1952 -- May 1955, 1952-06-1955-05 (Box 8, Folder 39-40)
    - January -- March 1951, 1951-01-1951-03 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - April 1951 -- June 1951, 1951-04-1951-06 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
    - July-September 1951, 1951-07-1951-09 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
    - October-December 1951, 1951-10-1951-12 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Selectiber Service 1951, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts for the Year ended May 31, 1951, 1951-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Examination of Accounts; Year ended May 31, 1952, 1952-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Chronological File September 1, 1953 -- December 31, 1953, 1953-09-01-1953-12-31 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Correspondence March 1953 -- April 1953, 1953-03-1953-04 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - April 1952 -- June 1952, 1952-04-1952-06 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Chronological Correspondence January-February 1953, 1953-01-1953-02 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Chronological Correspondence September 1953 -- December 1953, 1953-09-1953-12 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - TDS Monthly Reports June 1952 -- May 1953, 1952-06-1953-05 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - TDS Balance Sheet and Oper. Statements June 1952 -- May 31, 1955, 1952-06-1955-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Report on Examination of Accounts; Year ended May 31, 1953, 1953-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Survey Committee 1953--, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Auditor's Report May 31, 1954, 1954-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Manual of Accounts; Effective January 1, 1956, 1956-01-01 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence December 1956-1958, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence 1957, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Auditor's Report May 31, 1957, 1957-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Audit Report May 31, 1962, 1962-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Audit Report May 31, 1963, 1963-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Monthly Reports May 31, 1960 -- May 31, 1965, 1960-05-31-1965-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
    - DS Correspondence 1964, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 30-31)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Audit Report; May 31, 1964, 1964-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - DS Correspondence 1965, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs; Audit Report; May 31, 1965, 1965-05-31 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Barney Childs (misc.) 1965-1968, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Barney Childs Correspondence 1966-1967, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - DS Correspondence 1966, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Report on Financial Statements; May 31, 1966, 1966-05-31 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Barney Childs 1967, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence 1967, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Financial Statements May 31, 1967, 1967-05-31 (Box 10, Folder 6)